

Panji Iman Baskoro

Web Developer & Server Infrastructure Specialist

- About Me -

Hello my name is Panji Iman Baskoro I came from Malang. So I've been work on this industries almost 3 years . I have some interest in Server Infrastructure and Cloud Computing, maybe if I got position in this field it will be good opportunities for me.

- Internship Experience -

- PPTIK Brawijaya University (2015)
- Economic development of Batu City Goverment (2020)

- Organization Experience -

Research and Development Coordinator for SCeN 2018

- Contact -

Email:

Panjidia995@gmail.com

- Education -

Formal Education

- SDN Ngijo 1 (2005)
- SMPN 1 Karangploso (2011)
- SMKN 8 Malang (2014)

Informal Education

- Online Server infrastructure class in nolsatu.id (2018)
- Online SEO Course udemy (2019)

- Skills -

Programming

- Built web Application using PHP, Codeigniter, MySQL, AngularJS Asynchronous, PHP API & simple Microservices using python
- Version Controlling Service using Github
- Basic JAVA CLI & GUI

Server Infrastructure

- Manage Linux Server (Centos, Debian & Ubuntu)
- Manage container services using docker
- Optimize server management using vestaCP
- Basic CI/CD (Quality Assurance)
- Manage Cloud infrastructure in AWS and Alibaba Cloud

Others Skill

- Operating Microsoft Office and LibreOffice
- Project Management with Trello
- SEO, Social Media Marketing, Content Writer and Wordpress Optimization

- Working Experience -

Freelance

- Optimize Business process of a Company with building Information System for managing inventory and timeline process (2018-2019 & 2019-2020)
- Built Landing pages for antirayapmalang.com for optimize it's company marketing
- Sysadmin for quick count website pemilu2019.com, for Traveling agent startup in Malang and BUMN PTPN at surabaya
- SEO Engineer for textile company at Malang

Teaching

- Lecturer Adobe Flash CS 3 SMP PJ Global (Februari 2019 - Mei 2019)
- Lecturer PHP & HTML SMAN 1 Sumberpucung (November 2018 & Februari 2019)

- Public Speakers -

- Workshop Software Freedom day (SFD) 2019 Universitas Brawijaya: Implementasi Docker untuk pengembangan Software
- STIKI Goes To Campus 2018: SMKS ANNUQAYAH Sumenep Build Neat Server In Your Room
- STIKI Goes To Campus 2018 : SMKN 5 Malang Bounty Hunter
- STIKI Goes To School 2018 : SMKN 10 Malang Web Design Dasar
- STIKI Goes To School 2019: SMKN 10 Malang Teknik Informatika In A nutshell
- STIKI Goes To School 2019 : SMKN 3 Batu Teknik Informatika In A nutshell
- SSC 2019: 4.0 Industries for SMK